RoboForm Privacy Policy
=======================

PRIVACY POLICY: RoboForm is wholly owned and operated by Siber Systems Inc. (Siber), a Virginia Corporation located at 3701 Pender Drive, Suite 400, Fairfax, VA 22030, United States. DATA WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT: Customer is identified on Order Form, which is filled out by Customer when purchasing RoboForm products. Personal data of Customers that purchase RoboForm licenses is stored on Siber servers in the data center located in USA. Siber collects Email, Phone Number, Full Name for the purpose of account management and user support. Siber collects Email, Phone Number, Full Name, Address and Credit Card Number for payment processing: making purchases, refunds and chargebacks, activation and reactivation of RoboForm licenses. Siber collects Product Name, Full Name (as recorded in payment / license management system), Order ID (as recorded in payment / license management system), Email (as recorded in payment / license management system), Unique ID (GUID), Computer ID (generated via one-way function from some of the computer attributes), Disk ID (generated via one-way function from Disk ID of a system disk) for license activation and periodic license check. Siber collects Product Version, Internet Explorer Version, OS Version, Full Name (as recorded in payment / license management system), Email (as recorded in payment / license management system), Product Executable File name during product auto-update. User needs to opt-in to use that option. Siber only uses minimum of user data necessary to manage user account or to process payment. No other information is collected. HOW WE SHARE YOUR DATA: Siber will not send personal data stored on Siber servers to other companies or individuals, except for cases when sending of such data is required by Siber business processes. Siber discloses Email, Full Name, Phone Number and Address to Stripe which is credit card processor. Siber may also disclose Email and Full Name to MailChimp and IBM Watson for purposes of sending email. MARKETING: Siber will send infrequent product update newsletters and promotional offers to the email and postal addresses stored by Siber, but Customer shall have an option to unsubscribe from such email newsletters and offers. Siber will also present infrequent offers of Siber and 3rd party software on post-update web page that is shown when user installs new version of RoboForm. EUROPEAN UNION, UNITED KINGDOM AND SWISS INDIVIDUALS Siber Systems complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF) and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Siber Systems has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union and the United Kingdom in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. Siber Systems has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/. In compliance with the EU-US Data Privacy Framework Principles, Siber Systems commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information transferred to the United States pursuant to the DPF Principles. EU, UK and Swiss individuals with DPF inquiries or complaints should first contact Email: jwalls@siber.com Justin Walls Privacy Officer Via Post: Siber Systems Inc - Privacy Officer 3701 Pender Drive, Suite 400 Fairfax, VA 22030, USA Siber Systems has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the DPF Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, Data Privacy Framework Services, operated by BBB National Programs. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit https://bbbprograms.org/programs/all-programs/dpf-consumers/ProcessForConsumers for more information and to file a complaint. This service is provided free of charge to you. If your DPF complaint cannot be resolved through the above channels, under certain conditions, you may invoke binding arbitration for some residual claims not resolved by other redress mechanisms. See https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/G-Arbitration-Procedures-dpf?tabset-35584=2 \*\* TERMS OF USE \*\* PERSONAL DATA IN ROBOFORM WITHOUT SYNCHRONIZATION: NO TRANSMISSION, NO RECOVERY. All Password Data that Customer enters into RoboForm is stored only locally on Customer's computer if Customer does not use option to Synchronize RoboForm. In this case RoboForm does not transmit any Password Data over the Internet. However, if Customer or a program running on Customer's computer causes RoboForm to fill an online form with such personal data, then submission of this form will result in this data being sent over the Internet but this shall be deemed not to be caused by RoboForm. Customer agrees that deletion or loss of Password Data entered into RoboForm will cause irreversible loss of the said Password Data and Customer accepts the risk of such loss. PERSONAL DATA IN ROBOFORM WITH SYNCHRONIZATION: DATA TRANSMITTED, RECOVERY POSSIBLE. If Customer uses Synchronize RoboForm option then Customer Password Data is stored locally on Customer Computer or portable disk and on RoboForm server. If local copy of user data is lost, Customer may obtain copy of this data from RoboForm server. However, availability of backup copy is NOT guaranteed by Siber and Siber shall NOT be held liable, if it cannot produce copy of Customer's RoboForm data. Customer is hereby encouraged to keep multiple copies of RoboForm user data on his/her computers, disks and devices. Also in this case RoboForm shall transmit RoboForm Password Data over the Internet, for the purposes of storing backup copy of Customer RoboForm Password data on RoboForm server and for purposes of synchronization of said data between Customer computers and mobile devices. Customer hereby authorizes such transmission. ONLINE LICENSE ACTIVATION AND MONITORING: Customer hereby agrees to Online License Activation and Monitoring process for all RoboForm licenses (Personal, Family, for Business). In this process RoboForm checks the validity of Customer's RoboForm license by contacting the Siber server at \*.RoboForm.com via the Internet and sending data that uniquely identifies Customer's computer. Customer also agrees that Online Activation and Monitoring will be used to enforce provisions of this Agreement. TRANSMISSION OF DATA IN AUTOUPDATE: RoboForm automatically checks Siber's server www.RoboForm.com for new versions and security patches approximately once a day. If it finds a version that is newer than the version that is currently installed, RoboForm will suggest that Customer upgrades to the more recent version. The checking of new version results in various data related to computer and license to be transmitted to Siber server and maybe stored on this server. Customer hereby allows such data transmissions to occur. ROBOFORM WEB SITE: RoboForm web site may use cookies to track users and Customer agrees to that. RoboForm affiliates and advertisers may also use cookies and Customer agrees to that. RoboForm Web Site utilizes Google Analytics features, including Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting and Customer consents to this. Google provides a complete privacy policy and instructions on opting out of Google Analytics here: [https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html](https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

* Personal

* Business

* Compare

* Support

* Promo

* Company

find us on

LANGUAGE

  English

 Copyright © 1999 - 2024 Siber Systems, Inc. All rights reserved.  
3701 Pender Dr, Suite 400, Fairfax, VA 22030

Our website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website. [Review our Privacy Policy.](https://www.roboform.com/privacy-policy)

Got it

Pin or enable your RoboForm extension.

Pin the extension

or

Enable

Not redirected: [Click here to be redirected to the Extension Store](https://chrome.google.com/extensions/detail/pnlccmojcmeohlpggmfnbbiapkmbliob)
